Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2008-271
  - Auyeung, William, The N-terminal 17 Amino Acids of Huntingtin Exon 1 Mediate Efficient Aggregation and Interaction with the Chaperonin TRiC., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Margaux J., G-patch Domain Containing 8 is Required for Peripheral Myelination in Zebrafish., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Berhanu, Aaron Elias, Identification of Genes Required to Coordinate Replication and Cell Division in the Bacterium Bacillus subtilis., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Yvonne Yuh-Ru, Characterizing the Dynamic Processes of Chromatin Modification and Transcription Repression during the Midblastula Transition in Xenopus tropicalis., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Doris, Behaviorally Induced Changes in per1and per2 Gene Expression in the Suprachiasmatic Nucleus of Siberian Hamsters., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Chao, Jesse O., Investigating CG30349, a Novel Gene with a Potential Role in Drosophila Spermatogenesis., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Cortez, Brandon, Geographic and Seasonal Variation in the Reproductive Performance of Populations of the Wavy Turban Snail (Megastraea undosa) along the Vizcaino Peninsula, Baja California Sur, Mexico and Implications for Fishery Management., 5/9/2008 (Box 1)
  - Danford, Christopher J., Anthropogenic Ocean Acidification and its Effects on Calicifying Phytoplankton: the Response of Eight Coccolithophore Strains to Changing pH., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - DePasse, John Mason, Intron Sequence Variation in the Colias eurytheme Polymorphic Gene Phosphoglucose Isomerase., 5/16/2008 (Box 1)
  - Fan, Audrey, Molecular Mechanisms of Neuronal Targeting in the Drosophila Olfactory System., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Gu, Eugene, COMT Polymorphism Predicts Abnormal Cingulate Cortex Development and Longitudinal Decline in Attentional Function in 22q11.2 Deletion Syndrome., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Hoang, Phuong T., Gi-protein-coupled Receptor Signaling in Pancreatic Islet Development and Function., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Hornbeak, Kirsten Bree, Gender Differences in Facial Processing in Squirrel Monkeys (Samiri sciureus): Possible Implications for a Model of Autism., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Huang, Harriet, Comparing HIV-1 Coreceptor Tropism in Clinical Virus Isolates and Plasma Samples., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Jin, Michael Y., Exploiting the Nrf2-ARE System for Temporal Control of Gene Therapy Against Ischemia., 5/8/2008 (Box 1)
  - Karasov, Talia, The Evolution of Insecticide-resistance at the ace Locus in Drosophila melanogaster., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Katsnelson, Michael Alexander, Elucidation of the Role of the Gene CG16708 in WntD-mediated Embryonic Development of Drosophila melanogaster., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Julie, The Parkinsonism Gene Homolog, Irk-1, Regulates Polarized Localization of Synaptic Vesicle Proteins in C. elegans., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Kolibachuk, Julia, Determining the Bioactive Properties of Hydra Insulin-like Peptide 2: a Study of the Evolutionary Origins of Insulin Signaling., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Ladd, Jennifer Melissa, The Role of Ets Transcription Factors Erg and Fi-1 in the Differentiation of Human Mesenchymal Stem Cells., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Lazaro, Rondy Michael, Finding the Relationship between Lateral Patellar Displacement and Patellofemoral Pain Reduction due to Knee Bracing., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Le, Stephanie, Physiological Consequences of Intermediate Status in the Dominance Hierarchy of Astatotilapia burtoni, an African Cichlid Fish., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Malinda, The Effect of Food Deprivation on the Body, Brain and Behavior of the Model System Astatotilapia burtoni., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Lin, Tasha, Sex-specific Regulation of Fertility by fruitless-expressing Neurons in Drosophila., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Liu, Richard, Peptide Nucleic Acid Binding and Oligonucleotide Induced Mutagenesis in Repetitive DNA Sequence from Friedreich's Ataxia., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Luongo, Francisco, Identifying Transcription Factors Regulating Local Interneuron Development in the Drosophila Olfactory System., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Ma, Beijia, The Role of MicroRNAs in the Pathogenesis of Psoriasis., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Ma, Jeffrey H., The Role of GRAIL in the Induction of Anergic and Regulatory CD4+ Tumor-infiltrating Lymphocytes., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Melton, Ryan, Behavior and Androgen Response of Female Fish Follows Model of the Challenge Hypothesis., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Multhaup, Michael, Roles of the RabGEF1 ZnF and IUIM Domains in Mast Cell Activation., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Murthy, Ashwin C., In vivo Characterization of ß2 Adrenergic Receptor Cardiac Function via ß2 Adrenergic Receptor Knockout Mice., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Daniel A., Functional Connectivity Analysis of the Inferior Parietal Lobe: Determining the Resting State Connectivity of the Angular Gyrus, Supramarginal Gyrus, Anterior Parietal Sulcus, and Posterior Parietal Sulcus., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Olsen, Kendall Mary, Characterization of Pho88p Function and Interaction in Saccharomyces cerevisiae., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Perez, Alejandro, Comparison of Genomic DNA Isolation Strategies for AFLP Applications., 5/8/2008 (Box 2)
  - Pierce, Nuri Teresa, Venom Synthesis and Gene Expression Analysis of Peptide Toxins in Venom Ducts of Conus californicus Maintained in Tissue Culture., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Prugpichailers, Tiffany, Effects of VEGFR-Targeting Anti-Angiogenic Therapy on Temozolomide Delivery in the Treatment of Glioblastoma., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Qiu, Mary, Investigating the Role of SNAP-25 Interacting Protein in Synaptic Transmission in Caenorhabditis elegans., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Ramsey, Derek Christopher, Role of a Putative Formate Dehydrogenase in the Fermentative Hydrogen Metabolism of Shewanella oneidensis MR-1., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Rose, John C., The Role of AP-2 Transcription Factors in Taxane-Resistant Human Breast Carcinoma Variants., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Rosen, Miles, Unraveling Human Thermoregulatory Control: How Core and Ambient Temparture Affect the Vaoconstriction Threshold in Arteriovenous Anastomoses (AVAs) of the Human Hand- and the Subsequent Effect on Heat Transfer Ability., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Sindhu, Camille, Determination of Cell Surface Phenotypes of Granulocyte and Macrohage Progenitors Downstream of the Bipotential Granuloctye/Macrophage Progenitor., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Singh, Simar J., Humoral immunity and nerve regneration., 9/18/2008 (Box 3)
  - Srivastava, Shivani, The Role of Dysregulated Apoptosis in Systemic Juvenile Idiopathic Arthritis., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Sun, Catherine, Genetic Characterization and Mapping of Shifty, an Alteration in Airway Branching Pattern of C57BL/6J Mice., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Tao, Jessica J., The Epigenetic Mechanism of p15INK4b and p21CIP Regulation Before and After MYC Oncogene Inactivation in a Conditional Mouse Model of Cancer., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Tao, Li, Analysis of Endogenous Small RNAs in 'Wild-type' and RNAi-defective Mutants of Caenorhabditis elegans Using Barcoded Sequencing Design., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Thompson, Maxwell E., Identification of Candidate Protective Genes in Prostate Cancer through Comparative Expression Profiling of Seminal Vesicle., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Tom, Michael K., Ecological Impacts of French Broom Invasion Management., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Tsai, Jessica Whei, Effects of Light on Sleep and Wakefulness in Melanopsin-knockout Mice., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Tseng, Jocelyn M., The Role of the Johnston's Organ Neurons in Song-induced Courtship., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Vincent, Benjamin, Functional Characterization of Yeast Penta-EF Homolog Pef1., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Vinjamoori, Anant, Real-time Interrogation of Ligand-induced 1?Ba Dynamics and Kinetics Using a Transcriptionally-coupled Bioluminescent Reporter System., 5/8/2008 (Box 3)
  - Vitorovic, Stefan, Characterization of Hematopoietic Stem Cells., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Ping, Analysis of Sequences 5' of the doublesex Gene in Drosophila melanogaster., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Westmoreland, Lori Suzanne Hulden, Mytilus californianus: a Study of Marine Mussel Thermal Tolerance through Analysis of Heart Fuction, Enzyme Activity, and Genetics of Specimens from Boiler Bay, OR and Monterey Bay, CA., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Xiao, Harvey Han, Age, Dose, and Time-dependent Effects of Chromium Mesoporphyrin on Heme Oxgenase Activity in Mice., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Yilmaz, Melis, A Novel Role of unc-431 CaM Kinase II in Maintaining the Integrity of the Presynaptic Terminal in Caenorhabditis elegans., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Yu, Katherine, The Role of the Lateral Line on the Social Behavior of Astatotilapia burtoni, an African Cichlid Fish., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Zhang, Susan, Effects of RNA Secondary Structure on the Initiation of Translation in Eukaryotes., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
  - Zheng, Luo Luo, Cultivation of Rabbit Corneal Epithelial Cells and Surface Modification of a Hydrogel to Support Epithelialization on an Artifical Cornea., 5/8/2008 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2009-202
  - Awakuni, Jennifer, IL-17 induced PGC-1B expression: pro inflammatory role in DSS induced colitis., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Chiang, David, Regulatory T cells and primary immune deficiencies: an examination of Treg in common variable immunodeficiency and STAT5b deficiency., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Cole, Adam M., Byssal thread allocation decreases group tenacity in the ribbed mussel, Mytilus californianus., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Cox, David BT, Co-expression of CD47 and candidate brain cancer stem cells antigens in a preclinical model of human glioblastoma., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Doyle, Elizabeth, Role of GRAIL in FceRI-dependent responses in mouse mast cells., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Duc, Thinh Nguyen, Synthesis and evaluation of matriptase-selective activity-based probes., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Gaeta, Xavier, Inflammatory cytokine pretreatment alters CCR2 receptor externalization in neural stem cells for therapeutic delivery after stroke., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Germain, David Aaron, Polarized transport of dishevelled during planar cell polarity acquisition., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Gui, Dan Y, GTPase activity of NS3 is required for its role in growth control., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Hidgon, Lauren, Identification of distinct murine peritoneal macrophage subsets., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Ho, Andrew M, Regulated protein tracking in the endoplasmic reticulum (ER) associated protein degradation pathway., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Hoang, Tinya Audrey, Characterization of a DnaJ-related gene in the colonial ascidian Botryllus schlosseri., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Kamat, Nikhil V., Cardiac glycosides as novel anti-inflammatory agents in the treatment of collagen-induced arthritis., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Kamber, Roarke A., Intestinal microbiota and lifespan in a short-lived vertebrate model for aging, the African killifish Nothobranchius furzeri., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Karp, Daniel S., Sound the stressor: effects of ecotourist conversation on rainforest birds., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Kharsa, Zena, A novel and critical role for RNA polymerase III in the early embryo., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Khine, Htet, A search for genes that are diagnostic of male-sterile mutant anthers in Zea mays., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Kim, Arthur J., Plasma carboxypeptidase B down-regulates macrophage and osteoclast activation via osteopontin cleavage., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Klausner, Jill, The neurological and physiological effects of receiving social information in female fish., 2009 May (Box 1)
  - Kleiman-Weiner, Max, Synergistic roles of GABAa receptors and SK channels in regulating thalamocortical oscillations., 2009 June (Box 2)
  - Klotz, Adam C., Amyloid-B inhibits EPSP-spike potentiation in hippocampal CA1 neurons: a novel effect on synaptic plasticity in Alzheimer's disease., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Lin, Eric W., Functional analysis of immediate-early 63 protein of varicella-zoster virus., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Liu, Dianna, Mutagenesis spectrum of Caenorhabditis elegans., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Liu, Mengyuan Tommy, The effects of palmar heat extraction during upper body muscular resistance exercise on conditioning and strength., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Mamer, Lauren, The effect of peripheral macrophage signaling on stroke outcome., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Nevin, Zachary S., Variations in capsid uncoating of adeno-assocaited viurs serotypes 2, 8, 9 and DJ., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Pham, Betty Ngoc, The use of biomarkers in monitoring immune status and graft stability in liver transplant patients., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Ream, Micki, Davidson Seamount and beyond: biogeographic distribution of megafauna., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Ritchie, Cayde Daniel Matthew, Effect of selective and non-selective orexin receptor antagonists in the murine model: a sudy of potency and efficacy of OXR antagonists in pharmaceutical development for insomnia therapy., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Rodriguez, Stephanie, The role CDR3 flexibility in T cell receptor specificity and peptide-MHC binding., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Rominger, Andrew J., Both neural and deterministic processes drive community structure: tests and predictions from an aridland grasshopper community., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Shaikh, Nadia, Searching for sooy foot, a novel mouse mutation yielding p53-mediated dark skin., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Sofos, Elvera, Facilitated aggregation and induction of selective degradation by autophagy., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Sorrells, Trevor, The Mechanism of Chaperones on the translating yeast robosome., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Stanley, Susan E., Live cell imaging of pancreatic islet precursor cells., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Sun, Amy, Firefly luciferase-based dynamic bioluminescence imaging: a non-invasive technique to assess vessel permeability during tumor angiogenesis., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Sun, Matthew Zhuo, Investigation of the inhibitory properties of a Myelin-associated lipd, sulfatide., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Tang, Sherry, A novel intramolecular interaction in kinesin motor UNC-104 in C. elegans., 2009 May (Box 2)
  - Theologis, Aris, The effects of pulsatile flow on the organization of P19-derived cardiomyocytes., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Tran, Misha, Shedding light on the regulatory role of CSN5 in Myc-induced epidermal stem cell proliferation., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Wang, Kathleen, The hypothalamo-pituitary-adrenal and hypothalamo-pituitary-gonadal systems and brain function in postmenopausal women at genetic risk for Alzheimer's disease., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Yu, Emily Yang, Characterization of a Shewanella oneidensis [delta]cymA suppressor strain., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Zailani, Atiqah Nadiah, Recovery from bleaching: changes in symbiont composition present in the scleractinian coral, Montastraea franksi, over time., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Zarabi, Hosniya, Exploring the neural circuitry underlying depression using optogenetic techniques., 2009 May (Box 3)
  - Zhang, Pei, A GAGAa antagonist recovers learning and memory in arrhythmic Siberian hamsters., 2009 May (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2010-063
  - Bautz, Benjamin, Myeloperoxidase inhibition suppresses demyelation and clinical symptoms in murine experimental multiple sclerosis., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Bayne, Joseph, Identifying Novel Autoantigens in Rheumatoid Arthritis, Psoriatic Arthritis, and Ankylosing Spondylities., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Benkoski, Emmanuelle, Characterization of resistance mutant CG32706 of Drosophilia melanogaster in immune responses to various bacterial pathogens reveals melanization defect., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Bershad, Anya, Developmental Autonomy and Somatic Niche Construction Promotes Robust Cell Fate Decisions., 3/1/2010 (Box 1)
  - Boiko, Julie, IgG allotypes reveal that antimicrobial humoral immunity persists after reduced-intensity hematopoietic cell transplantation., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Brett, Jamie, Function and regulation of miR-106b~25 in adult neural stem cells., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Bulterys, Philip, Placental Malaria and Mother-to-Child Transmission of Human Immunodeficiency Virus Type 1 in Rural Rwanda AND Evidence of Extensive HIV Type 1 Subtype Diversity and Recombination in Rural Rwanda, 1989-1993., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Cantu, Andrea, Effects of Maternal Inflammation on the Developing Fetal Cortex., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Nicholas, Limb Remote Preconditioning Inhibits Tim-3/galectin-9 Expression and Blocks Free Radical Generation after Focal Cerebral Ischemia in Rats., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Shihwan, Function of cdh-6 gene in Axon Morphology of AFD AFD Thermosensory neuron in Caenorhabditis elegans., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Jonathan, Determining the Behavioral and Histological Effects of Lipopolysaccharide-Induced Inflammation in ATM Knockout Mice., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Cheng, Karen, CDKN2B is required for differentiation in human coronary artery smooth muscle cells., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Chu, Albert, Tumorigenic properties of cancer-derived JNK2a2 mutations., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Conlon, Erin, The Genetic Basis for Divergent Patterns of Overlapping Structural and Regulatory Variation of a Dimeric Esterase in Colias eurytheme., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Culbertson, Collin, RNAi knockdown of Prokineticin 2 and its effects on ischemic neuron death., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Davtyan, Arpine, The association of polymorphisms in circadian genes CLOCK and PERIOD3 and risk for developing pediatric bipolar disorder., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - de los Angeles, C. Paula, Genetic Analysis of Toxoplasma gondii Virulence Factor ROP5., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Del Raye, Gen, The Price of Migration: A new technique for estimating body lipid stores in migrating great white sharks (Carcharodon carcharias)., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Duong, Nina, Glucose-6-Phosphate-Dehydrogenase (G6PD): a sequence analysis and structural study of different alleles observed in Colias eurytheme and Colias meadii., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Eaton, Kelly, Neural Mechanisms of parental care and filial cannibalism in female fish., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Fero, Kelly, LytM factors in Caulobacter crescentus play a critical role in maintenance of proper peptidoglycan thickness and integrity., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Fisicaro, Ryan, Spectral Analysis of Electroencephalographic Activity in the Human Cortex to Describe Sleep Pathology and Countermeasures to Sleepiness., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Freret, Morgan, Novel neural precursor cell populations in the postnatal human pons., 11/30/2009 (Box 1)
  - Garcia, Jordan, The Role of NKG2D in NK Cell Interactions with Epstein-Barr Virus Infected B Cells., 5/14/2010 (Box 1)
  - Gillespie, Anna, Insulin-like Growth Factor Binding Protein 5 as a Potential Mediator of Tumor-Stroma Crosstalk in a Mouse Model of Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Graber, Madeline, Activity Levels of Serotonergic Neurons and Insulin-Producing Cells Affect Drosophila Body Size and Insulin Levels in the Brain., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - He, Cynthia, Effects of Zinc Deuteroporphyrin Bis Glycol on the Inhibition of Heme Oxygenase Activity and on Heme Oxygenase-1 Gene Expression in Heme-Loaded Newborn Mice., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Huang, Jennifer, Eotaxin and FGF enhance signaling through an Extracellular signal-related kinase (ERK)-dependent pathway in the pathogenesis of Eosinophilic Esophagitis., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Jiang, Hansi, Transposon Mutation in DivIB Suppresses Inhibition of Division Caused by YneA, a Bacillus subtilis SOS Response Protein., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Grace, The Effect of LincRNAs 4B on Epidermal Differentiation., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Kustan, Jacqueline, The Extent of Social Control of Spermatogenesis, Sperm Quality and Reproductive Competence in Astatotilapia burtoni., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Laidlaw, Grace, Identification of host proteins that are targeted by the Salmonella effector protein SseI during the inhibition of phagocytic cell migration., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Lau, Ashley, Evaluation of the Efficacy of Site-Specific Integrating Recombinant AAV Vectors for Gene Therapy Methods., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Leff, Maija, Characterization of a PAS-GGDEF-EAL domain protein in Shewanella oneidensis: Implications for metabolism., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Lichtinger-Velasco, Eric, The Role of GABA-B-mediated Inhibition in Isofurane-induced Depression of Hippocampal Responses., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Macway, Sarah, Evolution in Metabolic Pathways: Heterozygote advantage at the G6PD locus in male reproductive fitness of Colias eurytheme., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Mammo, Dagem, Tracking the Eye Position of Non-Human Primates: Comparing the Scleral Search Coil and Infrared Optical Techniques., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Ngai, Lynn, Transcriptional and Post-transcriptional Regulation of p130 Expression In Vivo., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Anthony, Modulating the ATP-binding affinity of the eukaryotic chaperonin, TRiC., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Hong-An, The role of excitatory synaptic inputs in the social regulation of preoptic area neurons in the cichlid fish, Astatotilapia burtoni., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Nghi, A Comparison of the Effects of Soluble and Tethered Jagged1 on Muscle Stem Cell Fate., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Quynh Anh Dac, Production of midbrain dopaminergic neurons from iPS cells derived from Parkinson's patients., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Rochelle, Identification of Inhibitors of Homologous Recombination for Radiation Therapy., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Nova, Philip, Caffeine intake, mood, and sleep in college students: caffeine-associated sleep disruption in modulated by chronotype., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - O'Neil, Christine, Reproduction of the coralline crust Pseudolithophyllum neofarlowii: factors and cycles of spatial and temporal variation., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Olayiwola, Tobi, Neuronal TGF-b Signaling Promotes Dendritic Development In Vitro., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Ongaigui, Kristine, Characterization of the effects of NF-kB blockade on aged skin., 5/14/2010 (Box 2)
  - Parsanian, Lucineh, Function of Racquetball, the Drosophila hnRNP R/Q homolog, in the male germline., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Pitt, Cameron, Exploration of No Tail-Dependent Genes and Their Roles in Notochord Differentiation., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Ponisio, Lauren, The effect of livestock grazing on the population and pollination dynamics of a montane butterfly, Speyeria mormonia (Lepidoptera: Nymphalidae)., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Rangel, Cuauhtzin, Investigating the Cognitive Effects of Pentylenetetrazol on Wild-Type Mice., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Roake, Caitlin, Exploring the Cellular and Molecular Mechanisms of Small Cell Lung Cancer Development Using Viral Vectors., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Russler, Emilie, Lineage and Intersectional Analyses of Drosophila melanogaster Olfactory Projection Neurons Using the Q-System., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Salinas-Rios, Viviana, Transcription in triplet nucleotide repeat DNA: Role in human genetic disease., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Schoen, Lucy, Characterization of the role of Glue15, a putative glucose transporter, in Arabidopsis Thaliana during bacterial infection., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Seki, Scott, Determining the Effect of Chronic Exposure to Air Pollution on Regulatory T cell Chemotaxis to the Airway in Asthmatic Children., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Shiu, Philip, Does Saccharomyces cerevisiae require positive feedback at mitotic entry? The role of early and late mitotic cyclins in activating CLB2 transcription., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Stegner, M. Allison, Using the Past to Predict the Future: Blue Grouse as a Model for Climate Change., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Tam, Jamie, Testing Single Nucleotide Polymorphisms in Humanized Yeast., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)
  - Thurber, Mary, Impact of Host Demographics and Rainfall on Fecal Strongyle Egg Counts in African Elephants (Loxodonta africana) in Namibia., 5/14/2010 (Box 3)